yahoo-mail.com.ng 2014-12-07

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy Statement for Yahoo-Mail.com.ng

Yahoo-Mail.com.ng has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Yahoo-Mail.com.ng

Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site, and to help identify you and your shopping cart. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes.

Our Site uses cookies to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies for other purposes.

Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Yahoo-Mail.com.ng is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).
